Guys, welcome back. It's been a while. I
have to get a message across to everyone
watching this video today, and that is
forget your all-time high P&L. I don't
know if you, you know, at the best and
peak moment of your, you know, this bull
run so far, you saw you had $40,000,
$5,000, a million, $3 million. Forget
it. Because everything to this point has
been a warm-up. It has been the pre-est.
It's been studying. It has been
preparation for what's going to come
because really we haven't even had an
alt season, man. This has Bitcoin
dominance over the last years. It's been
up only. And in that time, you have not
seen anything like 2021, which is this
right here. In 2021, Bitcoin dominance
went from 72 73% of all the money in
crypto in Bitcoin and then bam, only 40%
of the money in crypto was in Bitcoin.
That's what this ratio and chart
represents. And so we've been going up
for over a thousand days in Bitcoin
dominance, which means Bitcoin is
sucking up market share and altcoins and
meme coins are losing market share
during this time. And so the thing about
that is that once again, you're
expecting 2021 style returns, but we
haven't had the 2021 style or even close
to that type of environment. You see, so
that's the thing. I think people have
ridiculous expectations at the wrong
time. The thing is, your expectations
aren't wrong. They're just at the wrong
time. So, here's what you need to
understand in this video is that once
again, Brett and other meme coins that
you probably hold, like Pepe for
example, their whole entire existence
has only been when Bitcoin dominance has
been rising. They've never gotten to
experience an actual Bitcoin dominance
downturn where money shifts from Bitcoin
dominant uh times to altcoin dominant
times. And so you are over here giving
up on your memes in the hard times and
never even letting them see the good
times. And that is the biggest problem
that so many of you have. Giving up when
it's hard and never making it to the
times where times actually got easy. And
by the way, just these tiny little
glimpses that we've seen Bitcoin
dominance drop so far this cycle. For
example, the last time November to
December when Bitcoin dominance dropped
from 61% down to 54%.
This is what Brett did. It went from 700
million to 2.3 billion market cap. Just
this tiny little move, bro. And so
imagine when we get anything like this,
even a little bit bigger than this, we
get something like this. All right, this
right here is a 45% move down in Bitcoin
dominance. This right here, for example,
is a 20% move down in Bitcoin dominance.
This move right here was only 9%. You
see? And so all this in 2021 where you
made the big money was there, it's
there, it's there. So basically what I'm
trying to say is big money in altcoins
and memecoins or shitcoins or any of
these coins that are not Bitcoin is
going to happen in these moves down in
this chart. And once again, you're
giving up on your coins when they
haven't even we haven't even got a move
down in this chart. And so think about
that before you give up on some of your
coins. Think about that before you, you
know, you get sad about what your
all-time high peak portfolio value was.
Because dude, if it was 1 million in the
worst Bitcoin dominant environment,
which is I mean, it's the worst
environment for your altcoins, right? If
it was 1 million, then you're looking at
four to five to 6 to 7 8 million later.
And that's just simply based off this
chart coming down to not even the lows,
but back down to 48% these previous
highs in 2021 2022.
And so I'm just going to show you once
again the two runs a coin. It's just
it's crystal clear. For example, if you
look at May to June right here and you
look over here, May to June, whenever
Bitcoin dominance, it barely pulled
back. I don't even know if you can call
this a pullback. Brett pumps from 300
million to 1.9 billion. Then over here
in November to December, you have Brett
doing this in one single month. 700
million to 2.3 billion. Keep in mind
these only lasted about 1 month. Why?
Because Bitcoin dominance continues to
rise. But what happens whenever you
don't just get a one month tiny little
pullback and you get something more like
right here
130 days 300 days really or 600 days of
Bitcoin actually losing dominance. Of
course it has bounces in between but
what I'm really going to highlight is
this. This is the juiciest period right
here. 60 days. This is another juicy
period. 80 days. This is another period
right here. 60 days. You see, we're
going to have multiple of these waves.
And the wave is going to come in and
it's going to go out. It's going to come
in, it's going to go out. And and and
through those waves, in some waves,
you're going to have a moment where
gaming goes parabolic. In some moment,
memes go parabolic. In another moment,
you're going to have the new generation
of memes going parabolic. each of these
waves, there's different narratives and
different things that really pick up and
go the hardest. And so, once again, we
haven't had any of these true waves that
last even more than 30 days in the last
1,000 days. So, what I'm anticipating
and why I'm so confident Bitcoin
dominance is going to roll over is
because at the same time that Bitcoin
has been surging, right? Well, typically
what we've been seeing, Bitcoin has been
surging all this time and Bitcoin
dominance has been rising as well. But
for the first time in so long, we are
seeing Bitcoin is surging, but at the
same time, Bitcoin dominance is not
actually going higher, which means money
is starting to favor altcoins, meme
coins, and it's about to hit hard
because the truth is we're still very
close to the highs. But once this starts
to roll over, you're going to see an
enormous amount of money roll into your
alts. More money than even right here on
the same actual move. Why? Because right
now, Bitcoin is at a higher market cap.
It is at a higher price. And so that
means there is more money in actual the
crypto space. And so right now, for
example, 60% then is not going to be the
same as 60% now whenever Bitcoin is up
here in the hundreds, 20K plus. To put
it more simply, there's just going to be
a lot more money than you remembered or
have seen before. It's going to be a
wave that is going to make you feel
invincible. It's going to be a wave that
makes you feel like [__] is never going
to stop and like you can touch anything
and it turns to gold. That's the type of
environment you'll see and is going to
come soon. And one of the another reason
I'm really confident that's about to
happen is because one of my favorite
patterns uh in you know for shorting
something is this. Whenever it
overshoots the highs three times with
bare divergence aka it's getting weaker
even though it's going higher. You can
see that here went higher and got weaker
and then the volume is increasing on
that third top. So, for me, that's one
of the best setups to short something.
And although I can't short Bitcoin
dominance, it's not like a pair on BVID
or Binance. You go short it. What you
can do is then actually buy the altcoins
that you think are going to gain
dominance. How can we know what altcoins
are going to gain dominance is we can
pair them versus Bitcoin and look at
their chart. What I'm looking for before
I even pull into this chart on anything
that I pair versus Bitcoin, I am looking
for a long-term double bottom or
something that's already showing a clear
uptrend against Bitcoin. If it's not one
of those two things, it probably doesn't
make sense. And so, for example, in in
the case of Brett, this has to be one of
the most beautiful charts you could ever
buy if you know anything about buying
low and selling high. Because most
people obviously, what do they do? They
get hyped up and they always buy high.
They buy whenever the uh memecoin is
outperforming heavily Bitcoin. But what
you need to do is buy the lows, buy the
floor. You can see now for well over a
year, almost a year and a half, Brett
versus Bitcoin hasn't been able to go
below this low. Even with missiles
fired, even with Trump extracting
through his coin so much money from the
market, no matter what, it's been unable
to go lower than this level. And so this
gives you a floor to buy from where your
risk is very limited where you know you
can outperform so much and even just
coming back to the highs, right? You're
going to outperform Bitcoin by buying
Brett here by 5x. And that's just simply
returning back to the previous highs in
this pair. But that's not including
going past those highs. And so check
this out. This is a little hidden detail
that a lot of people are not going to
pick up on. When Brett hit 1.9 billion
market cap back here in June, go back to
this Brett over Bitcoin pair. This was
June. And you can see the highest point
in this pair was Brett hitting 1.9
billion. Then when the pair actually
went lower right here, it was still
hitting 2.3 billion. It was hitting
higher. And that's what I'm saying. Even
if we made a lower high here, you're
still hitting a higher market cap in
Brett because there is more money in the
space. There's more, you know, there's a
higher market cap. There's more money
flowing than there was before at the
same points in Bitcoin dominance. You
see? So we have to go back pull up the
Bitcoin dominance chart for example and
you can take a look at this for
yourself. But basically you can see even
when Bitcoin dominance rose from watch
remember this is the bottom point and
this is the top point. This is the
bottom point and this is the top point.
And so you can see even though Bitcoin
dominance rose and yet at the same time
even though Bitcoin dominance rose the
Brett top rose as well. Why? Because
once again there's more money in the
space. So you go further even with less
actual Bitcoin dominance. I mean I'm
sorry with more Bitcoin dominance you
still go higher because once again it's
more money pushing the prices of
everything. So that's what you need to
understand. Now, if we come back even
higher than before, we're going to be
already a higher market cap than the
previous highs and bread. But now, what
happens whenever this actually breaks
down? How high are you going to go then?
And so, this is another thing I want to
go over with everyone is how do you
actually sell at the top or close to it?
Because there's another chart I want to
point out which is going to help
everyone do that. And so if you take
USDT dominance plus USDC dominance,
basically what you're going to be
looking at is the combined percentage
that both of the largest stable coins in
the world make up out of the total
crypto market cap. So for example, you
can go over here to coin market cap and
you can see that the total market cap of
the entire industry right now is 3.74
trillion. Now take Tether and take USDC.
Together you add them up, they're around
220 billion market cap out of 3.74
trillion, which equals this right here.
6% of all market cap in crypto is shared
between these two stable coins. And so
whenever this chart right here bottoms,
the market tops. Whenever this chart
tops, the market uh bottoms. And so I'll
show you that real quickly. So look at
here, March 2024 and then December of
2024, this bottoms. If this bottoms,
that means more money is coming into
stable coins. And how does more money
come into stable coins? Obviously, it
means people are selling crypto and then
they're getting USDT or USDC. So when
people sell their crypto, this goes up.
Whenever people are getting rid of their
stable coins, this goes down. And
because they're getting rid of their
stable coins, what are they converting
it to? They're converting into Bitcoin.
So, let's go through this together.
March of 2024.
And then you go back to March of 2024.
Bitcoin tops as what? This bottoms. Then
we go back up here. July August of 2024.
July August of 2024. Bitcoin bottoms
whenever what this tops then it goes
back down. So once again, money is
leaving stable coins. It's going into
Bitcoin and crypto. And then bam,
bottoms by December, which means what?
Bam. Right here. By December, we top.
Then we come back up and April right
here, we set a top again. April, we set
a bottom again. You see how they're just
the opposite of each other. And so we
can get an extremely good idea of how
high Bitcoin and crypto is going to go
by looking at this chart. And basically
whenever you get to this support level
or slightly below it, that's when you're
going to be at support. That's when
you're going to be at a high-risk zone
where the chances of this chart
bottoming, right, are going to see this
is the thing about Bitcoin. There are no
resistance levels right now. you don't
have anything to go off of you. There's
no resistances above us. And so that's
where a lot of people get sucked into
looking at price targets. Oh, this guy
said it's going to hit 150K. This guy
said it's going to hit 500. This guy
said it's going to hit a million. And so
without any resistance level on this
chart to give you a good idea when is
the price going to stop. A lot of people
don't realize you can look at the stable
coin dominance and actually as it's
reaching the previous levels that's
where you're most likely to get
resistance on Bitcoin because you're
running into support on stable coin
dominance. You see? And so what's
probably going to happen is stable coin
dominance comes back to these levels
where it bounced from before slightly
below it give or take around there.
That's where you want to be taking
profits. So, everyone needs to, and you
don't even need a membership, a paid
one, right? To go on tradingview.com,
put in USDT.
D plus USDC.D. I'll do it again right
here.
And whenever you look at this chart,
since we have previous support levels
here, that's going to help us when we
run into unseen and unvisible resistance
levels that aren't there yet in the
chart on Bitcoin because it's in price
discovery. All right. So, that's a cool
little tip that a lot of people have no
idea uh how to look at because they're
only looking at, you know, if you think
about the typical person in crypto,
they're just looking at Bitcoin. They're
just looking at this chart and they see
no resistance. They see clear skies
above and they see a thing that just
keeps going up. What they don't see is
that support here equals future
resistance here. So pay attention to
this chart because it's going to help
you know when to sell not only just
Bitcoin but also altcoins even something
like Brett because by the time we get
down to around here Brett could already
be at 10x higher it could be at you know
40 cents to $130 for example when it
breaks out here and I think it's going
to break out any day any week. This is
the time where you have everything
shifted largely in your favor where
you're showing the inability to break
lower, but you have the ability to go a
lot higher. That's where you want to
buy. So 90% of people, they think that
alts and meme coins are so risky and
it's like hitting the lottery, but it is
for them because they're buying into
massive pumps against Bitcoin, which is
a bad strategy. You want to buy at
discount versus Bitcoin, not at a
premium versus Bitcoin because Bitcoin
is ultimately the asset that holds the
strongest long-term in crypto. So
imagine buying at a premium versus it.
You should be buying altcoins when you
have a discount versus Bitcoin. You see?
So obviously for most people though,
they get sucked into the hype and they
only buy whenever these things are
trading at a premium versus Bitcoin. If
you will shift and learn one thing from
this video, it is that if you're going
to buy risky [__] do it whenever it's
in your favor. Do it whenever these
things are showing you that they're
bottomed when they have the inability to
go lower and all the upside in the world
and that they're at a major discount
versus Bitcoin. Just like you would buy
Bitcoin or you should buy Bitcoin
whenever it was at a major discount
versus the US dollar whenever it traded
from 69K down to 16K. But oh wait,
nobody ever likes to buy the [__]
discount. Instead, what most people do
every time, they [__] on whatever is at
a big discount. They think, oh, because
it's a lower price, that mean must mean
it's not good or that it's dead or has
no traction. Then whenever the thing
goes up, oh yeah, dude, this [__] has
traction. This [__] is amazing. I'm
buying now. So you got to flip what the
90% of people in this world do and do
the opposite of them. When you do that
and you learn to bite down on the
mouthpiece and buy [__] whenever it's
not popular, well then whenever it gets
popular, that's when you win big. That's
whenever you make 10x, 20x, 30x, 50x is
by buying when shit's not popular
consensus and selling it and flipping it
to everyone when they badly want it from
you when it is consensus. And so this is
Brett versus Bitcoin. But Brett is not
the only chart like this. You can go and
you can look at other altcoin pairs and
see what is floored out with bullish
divergence. So for example, we can look
at Pepe versus Bitcoin and this is also
going to show us the same pattern. It's
at a major discount versus Bitcoin and
it has shown the inability to go lower
for almost half a year. It's been unable
to go lower. And so from this point,
obviously, what do you think has a
higher chance of happening? It's all of
a sudden just going to magically break
down below a level that it can't break
down from for over a, you know, half a
year or do you think, okay, it's shown
us that through missiles, through
Trumpcoin, it couldn't break down and
the more likely outcome is that now it's
going to gain dominance and pump against
Bitcoin like it has done so much in the
past. So once again, here's a pump
against Bitcoin, dump against Bitcoin,
pump against Bitcoin, dump against
Bitcoin, pump against Bitcoin, dump
against Bitcoin. This [__] moves in
waves. If you know how to surf here, if
you know how to get in and get out on
these waves, uh, instead of being the
one that buys into the wave, you prepare
for the wave and ride it. I mean, that's
the difference between being pro and
just being some noob who buys the top of
every meme and calls it a lottery or all
about luck. It's not luck. It's just
that most of you guys never look at
these charts, never look at the ratio of
your meme versus Bitcoin, and you never
pay attention to little details which
make a big difference. So, anyways,
enough of the charts. At this point,
there have been a 100 million gazillion
meme coins that launched. Every single
good narrative that there could possibly
be has already came out. There is only
going to be very occasional, in my
opinion, new narratives that happen
based off new world events. For example,
if Elon Musk gets a new dog or if there
is a new famous hippo that gets shot in
the zoo, something like that that
happens and that is relevant in that
time that's getting a lot of views and a
lot of attention and people fall in love
with the story. Outside of that, there's
not going to be new narratives. All the
best narratives, they already exist. So,
at this point, I think the best thing to
do is simply buy what has already went
through multiple big dips. Buy what is
proven. Buy what comes back every time
when the market is bullish. Buy what
people believe in after all those dips
still. And that's a short list of memes.
So, I really don't even need to tell you
what memes to buy. I can obviously I
have my own that I'm bullish on and you
can be bullish on whatever you want. I
really believe Brett is going to hit at
least a dollar this cycle and that's a
free 20x plus in my eyes. So, you know,
me, I I consider when or I I feel like
when you're right and you know you're
going to be right, you don't need to
take a million bets. You know, I have on
less than two hands meme coins that I
hold, less than 10. So, you guys can
spray and pray all you want. I know my
strategy. I'm buying Brett, Pepe, Bobo,
and a few others. And so, you can do
whatever you want. And at the end of the
day, I've shown you Bitcoin dominance.
I've shown you Tether and USDC dominance
combined, which will help you know when
to sell your crypto, including the coins
that I hold, including coins that other
people share with you, including coins
that you find on your own, and including
Bitcoin. This will give you a really
good idea of when to be taking some
profits uh off the table. And the truth
is, you should be up multiple X's.
Whether that's on Bitcoin you bought,
whether that's on Brett, whether that's
on any other meme coin that you've done
good on, you should be up many X's on by
now. So, as we approach this level,
you're going to be up even more X's. You
should be risk- free. You should have
your initial capital out and some profit
and you should have a good position
where once again, you can sleep on,
you're risk- free. And that's exactly
what's going to happen. It's going to be
impossible to not make money on Brett.
It's the number one meme on freaking
base and it is so undervalued compared
to every other number one meme right
now. So number one meme on uh in the
world, Doge, 29 billion. Number one meme
on ETH for now, SHIB, 7.8 billion.
Number one meme on Salana, 2.1 billion.
And then there's the next biggest chain
which is Bass. Number one meme, 540
million market cap. So B, you know,
Bread is by far the most undervalued
number one meme on its chain right now.
And it's going to catch up into the
billions like every other number one
meme on their chain. So for me, that is
the simplest, easiest, safest, highest
upside bet in the market, especially per
the market cap, right? Like if we're
talking about risk per size of the coin,
bread is by far the best bet in the
entire market in my opinion. And so I
fully believe you're going to see since
I've said from the beginning me turn
$15,000 into over $50 million plus
dollars on Brett this cycle which is
look my position is going to be worth 50
million in about a 12x. So Brett goes
from 500 million to just 6 billion 5
billionish market cap and I'm already at
a $50 million position in Brett. So,
this is really an easy target for Brett.
Um, and it's something that can go so
much farther than that because if you
think about the number one memes on the
other chains, okay, Doge 29 billion.
Obviously, that is way higher than uh
Brett at 6 billion, right? Okay. It's
the number one meme in literally the
entire world. Let's go through Pepe.
Pepe can hit 40 billion. And uh you know
what we saw in the last run when Pepe
hit 11 billion, uh Brett hit 2.3
billion. So Brett went 1 right 20% as
high as Pepe. So Pepe hits 40 billion
which is a 8x from here. Then Brett hits
8 billion. Let's say as a worst case it
does uh 20% of Pepe.
And then if it does 20% of Pepe that's 8
billion. Well right now 8 billion market
cap is right around here which is a
16x. Now, here's the weird here's the
real wild card factor is in 2021, SHIB
actually flipped Dogecoin momentarily
and a couple of times. And now,
obviously, do ship trades at a fraction
of Doge. But there were moments where
ship flipped Doge. And so now I'm giving
you a ratio. If Pepe hits 40 billion,
Brett hits just 20% of that, hits 8
billion. Right? Now, if Pepe hits 40
billion and Brett hits 50% of that,
Brett hits 20 billion, right? Once
again, SHIB was second to Doge, Brett
currently is second biggest character in
the comic next to Pepe. It's the number
one meme on base. This is the number one
meme on ETH. So, is it possible to see
Brett hitting 50 to 100% the market cap
of Pepe? Even if hitting 100% is only
momentarily, maybe it only lasts 3 days,
kind of like SHIB did to Doge. If you
believe that's a possibility, then the
upside for Brett, it can go anywhere
from 8 billion on the low end to 40
billion like Pepe on the high end. And
so that's what I am, you know, just,
bro, I is the comfiest, easiest hold in
the entire world. I mean, you have a
coin that has spent 99% of its life now
above a 500 to a billion market cap. You
have a coin that survived all the bad
catalyst uh for meme coins where 99% of
memes died and still stands strong as
the number one meme on base and holding
500 million floor. So, first off, in a
alt, you know, in a Bitcoin dominance
environment where it goes down, pretty
much almost every altcoin, you know,
5x's, 3x's. Now, the best altcoins like
the number one meme on base, number one
meme on Ethereum, these are going to do
even more X's than that. So, if the
typical coin does like a 3x, then these
coins are going to be doing minimum 8 to
10x. And that's worst case, I believe.
So, once again, people are not ready for
a real move in Bitcoin dominance. people
are going to be pissed that they sold
the bottom on so many coins or that
maybe they didn't even want to sell the
bottom, but they got so desperate they
ended up selling it to try and chase
different opportunities or gamble or try
to make money a different way. And then
they come back and say, "Damn, if only I
had held, I would have had x amount.
[__] me. I ruined it. I ruined the whole
cycle is what a lot of people are going
to say." So, it is what it is. I try to
make this video and other videos to help
try to help you understand how you can
actually know when to sell without
having to listen to anyone's price
targets. Okay, forget the price targets.
Focus on the levels because whenever
this reaches closer to support, that's
when you want to be taking profits,
whether it's on Brett or Bitcoin or
other things. And especially when
Bitcoin dominance gets closer to 50% or
lower, you know, those are your two
major signals. Okay, Bitcoin dominance
had a huge move down to 50% or less.
USDT dominance and circle dominance came
down to support at 4.5% or lower, taking
profits, right? And so then it doesn't
really matter whose price targets in the
world, whether they say 6 billion, 40
billion, 10 billion. Some people are
going to say they're going to flip the
[__] stocks. I mean, you know, stupid
[__] People are going to say it doesn't
really matter. Focus on the levels and
everything will work out. So, all right
guys, hope you enjoyed the video. Drop a
like. Make sure you subscribe. Follow me
on Twitter if you're not already. And
we're about to make a lot of freaking
money in the next 6 months. So, I hope
you learned and I hope this video helps
you sell uh at the right time and come
back in the future, whether that's
leaving me a comment on Twitter or
leaving a comment on this video or
future video and and tell me like, "Hey,
I ended up selling and not round
tripping thanks to this video." and that
would make me really happy. So, see you
guys later. Take care.